radio-south-africa.co.za 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy - Listen to radio online

#### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our websites/apps. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, location, device info, OS version, and other technical information about users. We also collect information, such as anonymous usage statistics, by using cookies, server logs, or other similar technology.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters. In order to improve your experience, when you visit our websites/apps, we may use cookies to store data such as your IP address and referring website address, browser type, domain name. We may use both session cookies (disappear after you close your browser) and persistent cookies (used by your browser on subsequent visits). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your settings (e.g. navigating in anonymous mode or changing your IDFA settings). We use cookies to track usage patterns and to control the display of ads, as well as to offer other functionalities.

Third parties that advertise goods or services in our websites/apps may also use cookies to track your use of the service. We advise you to check the privacy policies of these advertisers for information about their cookie usage and other privacy practices. Advertisers may also use cookies to track your online activities across websites over time to provide interest-based advertising.

We use third-party cookies to collect aggregated statistics in analysis tools such as Google Analytics. If you do not want Google Analytics to collect and use information about your use of the service, then you can install an opt-out in your web browser (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

#### How we use collected information

We may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To operate, maintain and enhance the service.
  * To provide support and improve customer service.
  * The apps can share collected location and bluetooth data for interest-based advertising allowing advertisers to infer interests and serve ads to users based on their app activity and location data over time.
  * Carry out other purposes that are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

#### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, and data stored on our websites/apps.

  * To prevent the collection of Location Information on iOS mobile devices, disable the location services feature on the settings of your device.
  * To prevent the collection of Location Information on Android devices disable Bluetooth and Location.
  * On iOS devices you can opt-out from any interest-based advertising. Go on Settings. Privacy, Advertising and then click on "Limit Ad-tracking". When you have opted out using this setting on a device, advertisers will not use in-app information collected from that device to infer your interests or serve ads to that device that are targeted based on your inferred interests.

#### Sharing your personal information

We may share the information we collect with third-party business partners who commit to comply with applicable laws concerning their usage of the information. Our third-party business partners may use the information either for themselves or on behalf of their own business partners to: 

  * Operate and improve their services;
  * Provide you with advertisements and information for products and services or send you other notifications based on variables such as your location, and assess your level of engagement with them;
  * Carry out other purposes that are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

This privacy policy can be updated at any time. When so, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of those modifications.

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using our websites/apps, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use our websites/apps. Your continued use of the websites/apps following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

#### Your rights

Pursuant to data protection laws, you have the right to access, modify, rectify and delete any of your individual data we might possess. To do so, as well as any questions about this Privacy Policy, please use the contact form.
